

Henrik Mjaaland

Computer Engineer

18 November 1993



Høgevollsveien 19B, 4315 Sandnes, Rogaland



+47 90215974



http://github.com/henmja



henrikmjaaland@hotmail.com

About Me ———

I am a computer engineer from Sandnes, Norway. I have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science, and I handed in my master's thesis this spring. For my master's thesis I wrote about fake news detection in social media using neural networks. The thesis is available on github: https://www.github.com/henmja.I have previously worked as a production operator, seller, gardener, and as a warehouse worker. Presently, I am working as a control technician for Nærbø Kyllingslakt. There, the tasks are IT-related (i.e. control the assembly lines).

Skills ——— Python Java **MATLAB**

Go

Javascript

PHP

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Key Qualifications

Solution-Oriented Disciplined Adaptable

Education

2017-2020 M.Sc. University of Stavanger

Computer Science

2014-2016 B.Sc.

Computer Science

University of Stavanger

Sandnes VGS

REMA 1000 Distribusion

Realfag

2009-2012 General Studies (Science)

Portfolio

https://www.github.com/henmja

Website

https://www.henrikmjaaland.com

Certificates |

2012	Driver's License, Class B
2012	Forklift License, T1
2016	Boating License

Experience

Current	Control Technician	Nærbø Kyllingslakt
2017-18	Production Operator	Nortura Forus
2016	Gardener	Facility Services
2015	Warehouse Worker	Megaflis Forus
2013-14	Seller	Burger Pizza Companiet

References

2012

References are given on demand.

Warehouse Worker